what rad oh I gotta check it back out
alright guys hahaha I already look this
doesn't have anything okay well alright
guys you see that Prius over there you
see this Ford Fusion
we're gonna start over there and we're
gonna race first person to cross that
red thing oh and after the red thing you
got to break pretty hard just you don't
have that much runoff room but it's fine
these cars don't get up to that high
speeds okay guys let's go let's go let's
go to the starting line
do it gonna leave the Prius in the dust
all right does anyone wanna bet does
anyone want to bet will it be the Prius
or the Ford Fusion
I don't have any sport mode in this car
I'm Harold your taxes are all in the
back there oh we gotta close the windows
for aerodynamics you wait do you keep
the windows open for hair dynamix close
the windows definitely closed all right
all right so how do we how do we start
okay I'll be the arbiter I'll do my hand
up and when it goes forward we start
wait but wait wait both of us with
windows open okay so my hands up and in
about 10 seconds it'll go down wait you
gotta pay attention to oh no I can't rub
the engine in this guy confusion
[Music]
alrights copies all right guys
will it be in the future will it be the
Prius in a photo finish all right guys
we're gonna stand here this is the
ultimate challenge will it be Japanese
engineering or will it be American
Muscle you decide or actually the cars
will decide okay
don't worry guys I'm gonna get over
there I'm gonna stay safely behind the
thing we got the fusion on the right we
got the priests and here they come in
here they come fusion on the left right
we got a Prius up left looking for that
photo finish here the cars here are the
cars here they come and yup it's not
even close it's the fusion thank you for
joining back on AI moments later